Guide to the George E. Stonebridge Photograph Collection 1897-1918 (Bulk 1899-1904) PR 66
New-York Historical Society
George E. Stonebridge Photograph Collection
1897-1918 (Bulk 1899-1904)
1899-1904
New-York Historical Society
PR 66
33 Linear feet (4,578 4 x 5" glass negatives; 8 2 x 3" acetate negatives; 40 4 x 5" glass positives; 2288 4 x5" vintage prints; 4 8 x 10" vintage prints; 94 vintage mounted prints; 76 8 x 10" modern copy prints; 1 small photograph album; and 1 photographer's logbook)
Stonebridge's work preserves scenes of outdoor family activities and local events in the Bronx. A sample of subjects includes Bronx parks, Croton dam strike, Brooklyn Navy Yard, funeral of General Franz Sigel, Dewey Naval and Land Parade, Niagara Falls, Jerome Park, Van Cortlandt Park, May Walk 1898-1899, Cycle Parade 1897-1898, wrecks, fires, Sportsman's Show, Stevens airship, Fordham, portraits, Orchard Beach, City Island, clubs, houses, churches, gas works (where Stonebridge was employed), New York Zoological Park, state militia camps and activities, the Seventh Regiment and Riverside Park. There are also baseball teams in action, scenes from Garrison, N.Y., and grim views of the "General Slocum" steamboat disaster victims Glass negatives and positives from the George E. Stonebridge Photograph Collection are digitized and available in the Shelby White and Leon Levy Digital Library.
Provenance
Gift, January 1942.
Access Restrictions
Materials in this collection may be stored offsite. For more information on making arrangements to consult them, please visit www.nyhistory.org/library/visit.
Biographical Note
George Ehler Stonebridge (d. 1941) was an amateur photographer who lived and worked in the Bronx, New York. He left little record of himself, but an invaluable one of his surroundings and interests.
Stonebridge lived at several locations in the Bronx with his wife Bella, and their three children Grace, George, and William. He worked at the Northern Gaslight Company, although the position he held is unknown. In addition to taking photographs, Stonebridge wrote poetry and prose about his love of the Bronx, his children, and in honor of military victories.
Some of Stonebridge's photographs appeared in local papers. In 1898, he was an authorized reporter and photographer for the North Side News; in 1905 he was an authorized reporter for the Bronx Borough Record and Times, and probably took photographs for that paper as well.
Stonebridge was fascinated with the subject of military preparedness. Training rituals and staged battles were one of his favorite photographic subjects. His 1898 poem, "Remember the Maine," celebrates the United States' victory in the Spanish-American War. He was especially proud of soldiers from the Bronx, and photographed historical tablets throughout the Borough commemorating previous military victories. Stonebridge also used his photographs to illustrate lectures. In 1907, he gave several lectures on "The Training of War," using colored lantern slides.
Scope and Content Note
The bulk of this collection consists of glass plate negatives. The photographs document both everyday life and special events, such as parades, in the Bronx and throughout New York state, from the end of the nineteenth century to the beginning decades of the twentieth century. Standard New York scenes of the time period are depicted, such as the Brooklyn Bridge, Central Park, Coney Island, and Riverside Park, but most views are in the Bronx.
Stonebridge's fascination with military matters shows in the breadth, and the number, of military subjects he shot. Photos show troops staging sham battles and engaging in practice maneuvers at camps. Special military events, many in connection with the Spanish American War, are also well represented. Stonebridge photographed the memorial arch erected in Madison Square in Manhattan to honor Commodore George Dewey, as well as the Land and Naval Parades held in 1899 to celebrate Dewey's victories in the Philippines. Stonebridge also photographed the funeral of Civil War General Franz Sigel, held on 24 August 1902, and the military ships docked in the Brooklyn Navy Yard.
Stonebridge was interested in documenting disasters, such as train wrecks and fires. He managed to capture some of the sense of chaos and trauma that resulted from the fire on board the wooden excursion boat General Slocum on June 15, 1904. Over 1,000 people, mainly women and children, were burned to death or drowned. Stonebridge's photos show bodies being recovered from the water, families identifying bodies and clothing, and much of the rescue effort.
Many of Stonebridge's subjects were familiar Bronx views or projects. The building of the Bronx Zoological Garden and of the New York Botanical Garden are well documented. Pictures of the zoo construction show construction workers, inspectors, and the animals on display. Events or landscapes in Van Cortlandt, Crotona, Jerome, and Claremont parks are documented. Some of these parks were used for both military and civilian purposes. The construction of bridges over the Harlem River is shown in several series. Washington Bridge and High Bridge are well represented. Photographs of houses and streets in the Bronx neighborhoods of Fordham and Tremont show daily life and architectural details of the area. Stonebridge's employer, the Northern Gaslight Company, is also represented.
Like perhaps any photographer, Stonebridge took many photos of his family, especially when his three children were young. In addition, the family spent time in Garrison, New York, perhaps with extended family or at a vacation house in the country. Photos show the children engaged in play with farm animals and goofing around for the camera. In February 1905. Stonebridge built a snow house in his yard, and the children are shown playing on top of and inside the structure. Two contemporary newspaper reports about the snow house are filed with the mounted photographs.
Excursions and trips to the beach, both small and large scale, are shown in many of the series of photographs in this collection. The largest group pertains to Orchard Beach at City Island, where Stonebridge's family and many others stayed in tents, sailed, played games, and relaxed. The photographs from this locale date from 1907-1916, as the family returned year after year, often for Labor Day festivities. The Stonebridge family is also pictured at the beach in Ocean City, New Jersey. Larger, multiple family excursions to other Bronx beaches, such as Locust Grove, and Port Morris are shown. Stonebridge also photographed Niagara Falls, already quite a well-photographed tourist attraction.
Sport activities are also well represented. Stonebridge photographed bicyclists (he seems to have been an avid cycler himself), ice skaters, and children playing baseball. He also took pictures of races at a speedway, an airship exhibition, gardens and gardeners. Photographs also cover more mundane subjects such as portraits, street scenes, churches, club buildings, and houses.
In addition to photographic material, the collection includes a logbook of photographs kept by Stonebridge, and a number of his grammar school records and certificates of merit.
Arrangement
Negatives and positives were matched to numbered descriptions in Stonebridge's log. Any negatives or positives left unmatched were then assigned titles and numbers by N-YHS staff. These titles and numbers were added to a photocopy of Stonebridge's log. This final listing, along with a clean copy of the original log, is available in the Print Room Collection files. However, all information has been entered into a Microsoft Access database for easier reference. Many numbers remain unassigned.
All formats are filed in this numerical order. Indices of series titles and number of items in each series can be found as addenda to this finding aid. More detailed searching can be done in the item-level database.
The Microsoft Access database lists each view by Stonebridge's own (or N-YHS given, if necessary) number and title. The formats each view appears in are noted. Titles written in Stonebridge's log that have not been located in physical form are not entered into the database. Titles assigned by N-YHS staff are bracketed, and marked in the database as such.
Missing Title
Series I: Glass Negatives
Series II: Glass Positives
Series III: Prints and manuscripts
Related Material at the The New-York Historical Society
Lantern slides and glass stereograph views by Stonebridge have been incorporated into the N-YHS Print Room's Transparency File (PR-070). Twenty rewards of merit issued to Stonebridge by the Morrisania School District are in the Print Room's Certificate File (PR-014).
The Manuscript Department of the N-YHS Library has a small group of Stonebridge family account books and miscellaneous letters. Call phrase: AHMC - Stonebridge, George E.; Title: George Ehler Stonebridge collection, MS 2958.9333.
Stonebridge donated many objects (military memorabilia, camera equipment, pillowcases printed with photographs) to N-YHS which are in the museum collection. A list of these items is available in the Print Room Collection file.
negatives (photographs); Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Description and travel.; Portraits.; Gelatin silver prints.; Niagara Falls (N.Y. and Ont.) -- Description and travel.; Memorial Day.; Families -- New York (State) -- New York.; Airships -- New York (State) -- New York.; Ships -- Fires and fire prevention -- New York (State) -- New York.; Ships -- New York (State) -- New York.; Churches -- New York (State) -- New York.; Dwellings -- New York (State) -- New York.; Beaches -- New York (State) -- New York.; Recreation -- New York (State) -- New York.; Soldiers -- New York (State); Military camps -- New York (State); Cycling -- New York (State); Gas manufacture and works -- New York (State) -- New York.; Baseball -- New York (State) -- New York.; Parades -- New York (State) -- New York.; Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Buildings, structures, etc.; Fordham (New York, N.Y.); City Island (New York, N.Y.); Van Cortlandt Park (New York, N.Y.); Parks -- New York (State) -- New York.; Jerome Park (New York, N.Y.); Riverside Park (New York, N.Y.); Garrison (N.Y.) -- Description and travel.; Photographic prints.; New York (N.Y.) -- Description and travel.; United States. Army. New York Infantry Regiment, 7th (Militia) (1806-1922); New York (State). National Guard. Artillery; New York (State). National Guard -- Drill and tactics; New York (State). National Guard -- Military life; New York Botanical Garden; New York Naval Shipyard; New York Zoological Society; Sigel, Franz, 1824-1902 -- Death and burial
- Series I: Glass Negatives
  Scope and Contents note
  The descriptions below are Stonebridge's actual series titles; those in brackets were assigned by N-YHS.
  Existence and Location of Copies
  Digital copies of glass negatives are available in the Shelby White and Leon Levy Digital Library.
  - Bronx Park, 1902-1904 (Box 1)
  - Bronx Park, 1902-1904 (Box 2)
  - Bronx Park, 1902-1904 (Box 3)
  - [Washington Bridge], undated (Box 3)
  - Camp Block, 1898 May 14 (Box 3)
  - Camp Block, 1898 May 14 (Box 4)
  - Fort Slocum, 1898 (Box 4)
  - Fort Slocum, 1898 (Box 5)
  - [Decoration Day], 1903-1911 (Box 5)
  - [Decoration Day], 1903-1911 (Box 6)
  - Sham Battle, Van Cortlandt Park, 1897-1901 (Box 6)
  - Sham Battle, Van Cortlandt Park, 1897-1901 (Box 7)
  - Croton Cornell Dam Strike, 1900 Apr. 21 (Box 7)
  - 2nd Battery, 1899 (Box 7)
  - Navy Yard, undated (Box 7)
  - Navy Yard, undated (Box 8)
  - [Fordham, Bronx], undated (Box 8)
  - [Fordham, Bronx], undated (Box 9)
  - Sham Battle, Van Cortlandt Park, 1902 (Box 9)
  - West Point, 1908, Jun. 4 (Box 9)
  - Funeral of General Franz Sigel, 1902 Aug. 24 (Box 9)
  - [Municipal Building], undated (Box 9)
  - [Canal], undated (Box 9)
  - [Canal], undated (Box 10)
  - [Baseball Game and Team], undated (Box 10)
  - [Miscellaneous Shoreline], undated (Box 10)
  - 2nd Battery, 1902-1903 (Box 10)
  - [Building trolley, train lines], undated (Box 10)
  - [Snow House], 1905 Feb. 1-1905 Feb. 29 (Box 10)
  - Porter Monument, 1902 Nov. 15 (Box 10)
  - [Snow House], 1905 Feb. 1-1905 Feb. 29 (Box 10)
  - [Miscellaneous, unidentified images], undated (Box 10)
  - [Miscellaneous, unidentified images], undated (Box 11)
  - Dewey Naval Parade, 1899 Sep. 29 (Box 11)
  - Dewey Land Parade, 1899 Sep. 30 (Box 11)
  - Dewey Land Parade, 1899 Sep. 30 (Box 12)
  - Dewey Arch, 1899 Sep. 1-1899 Sep. 30 (Box 12)
  - New York Zoological Park, 1899-1902 (Box 12)
  - New York Zoological Park, 1899-1902 (Box 13)
  - New York Zoological Park, 1899-1902 (Box 14)
  - New York Zoological Park, 1899-1902 (Box 15)
  - New York Zoological Park, 1899-1902 (Box 16)
  - New York Zoological Park, 1899-1902 (Box 17)
  - Niagara, undated (Box 18)
  - Niagara, undated (Box 19)
  - Decoration Day, 1899-1902 (Box 19)
  - Jerome Park, undated (Box 19)
  - Jerome Park, undated (Box 20)
  - Claremont, 1903 (Box 20)
  - Crotona, [1900] (Box 20)
  - Crotona, [1900] (Box 21)
  - Van Cortlandt Park, 1902-1918 (Box 21)
  - Van Cortlandt Park, 1902-1918 (Box 22)
  - Riverside Park, 1897 (Box 22)
  - Lohbauers, 1898-1899 (Box 22)
  - Excursion, Roton Point, Locust Grove, 1903 Jul. 7 (Box 22)
  - Excursion, Roton Point, Locust Grove, 1903, Jul. 7 (Box 23)
  - May Walk, 1898-9, 1898-1899 (Box 23)
  - Cycle Parade, 1897-8, 1897-1898 (Box 23)
  - Cycle Parade, 1897-8, 1897-1898 (Box 24)
  - Speedway, undated (Box 24)
  - Coney Island, 1903 (Box 24)
  - Coney Island, 1903 (Box 25)
  - Brooklyn Bridge, undated (Box 25)
  - Port Morris, Oak Point, undated (Box 25)
  - Harlem River, undated (Box 25)
  - Harlem River, undated (Box 26)
  - Wrecks, 1902 Jun. 14 (Box 26)
  - Heine Fountain, Cornerstone, St. Joseph's, 1899 (Box 26)
  - 6th Heavy Artillery, undated (Box 26)
  - Fires, 1902 (Box 26)
  - Fires, 1902 (Box 27)
  - Sportsman's Show, 1902 Mar. 15 (Box 27)
  - Hohenzollern, Stevens Airship, 1902 (Box 27)
  - Hohenzollern, Stevens Airship, 1902 (Box 28)
  - Botanical Garden, [1900] (Box 28)
  - [Stonebridge Family Gardens], undated (Box 28)
  - Tremont, [1902] (Box 28)
  - Tremont, [1902] (Box 29)
  - Fordham, [1902] (Box 29)
  - Pelham, City Island, Bartow, Westchester, 1903-1907 (Box 29)
  - Pelham, City Island, Bartow, Westchester, 1903-1907 (Box 30)
  - Houses, undated (Box 30)
  - Houses, undated (Box 31)
  - Portraits, undated (Box 31)
  - Portraits, undated (Box 32)
  - Portraits, undated (Box 33)
  - Creedmoor, 1899-1904 (Box 33)
  - Creedmoor, 1899-1904 (Box 34)
  - Creedmoor, 1899-1904 (Box 35)
  - Creedmoor, 1899-1904 (Box 36)
  - 2nd Battery, 1899 (Box 36)
  - State Camp, 1899-1904 (Box 36)
  - State Camp, 1899-1904 (Box 37)
  - State Camp, 1899-1904 (Box 38)
  - State Camp, 1899-1904 (Box 39)
  - Garrison (Box 39)
  - Garrison, 1900-1906 (Box 40)
  - Garrison, 1900-1906 (Box 41)
  - Garrison, 1900-1906 (Box 42)
  - Garrison, 1900-1906 (Box 43)
  - Family Portraits, undated (Box 43)
  - Family Portraits, undated (Box 44)
  - Family Portraits, undated (Box 45)
  - Family Portraits, undated (Box 46)
  - Family Portraits, undated (Box 47)
  - [Clove Road, Brooklyn, NY], undated (Box 47)
  - [Tablets in parks], 1913, Apr. 19 (Box 47)
  - [Liberty Bell], 1903 (Box 47)
  - [Ocean City, NJ], undated (Box 47)
  - City Island, undated (Box 47)
  - City Island, undated (Box 48)
  - Orchard Beach, City Island, 1907-1916 (Box 48)
  - Orchard Beach, City Island, 1907-1916 (Box 49)
  - Orchard Beach, City Island, 1907-1916 (Box 50)
  - Orchard Beach, City Island, 1907-1916 (Box 51)
  - Orchard Beach, City Island, 1907-1916 (Box 52)
  - Orchard Beach, City Island, 1907-1916 (Box 53)
  - Houses, undated (Box 53)
  - Harts Island, 1913 Jul. 12 (Box 53)
  - Harts Island, 1913 Jul. 12 (Box 54)
  - Maggie Nolan], 1903 Jul. 24 (Box 54)
  - Highbridge, [1900] (Box 54)
  - Clubs in the Bronx, [1903] (Box 54)
  - Clubs in the Bronx, [1903] (Box 55)
  - NY Central Railroad, 1903 (Box 55)
  - Gas Works, [1900] (Box 55)
  - Bridge under construction, [1903] (Box 55)
  - Bridge under construction, [1903] (Box 56)
  - [Miscellaneous Bridges], undated (Box 56)
  - Echo Park Flag Raising, 1903, Nov. 26 (Box 56)
  - Excursion to Roton Point, undated (Box 56)
  - Manhattan, 1899-1901 (Box 56)
  - [Poughkeepsie], undated (Box 56)
  - Garrison, 1910 (Box 56)
  - Garrison, 1902-1914 (Box 57)
  - Churches, [1900] (Box 57)
  - Churches, [1900] (Box 58)
  - State Camp, 1904-1905 (Box 58)
  - State Camp, 1903-1915 (Box 59)
  - State Camp, 1903-1907 (Box 60)
  - State Camp, undated (Box 61)
  - Portraits, undated (Box 61)
  - Portraits, 1903-1906 (Box 62)
  - Family Portraits, undated (Box 62)
  - Family Portraits, undated (Box 63)
  - [Bronx], undated (Box 63)
  - [Bronx], undated (Box 64)
  - [General Slocum Disaster], 1904 Jun. (Box 64)
  - [General Slocum Disaster], 1904 Jun. (Box 65)
  - [Pillow Tops], undated (Box 65)
  - [Pillow Tops], undated (Box 66)
  - [Collages of Stonebridge Prints], undated (Box 66)
- Series II: Glass Positives
  Digital copies of glass positives are available in the Shelby White and Leon Levy Digital Library.
  - Bronx Park, 1902-1904 (Box 66)
  - Fort Slocum, 1898 (Box 66)
  - Navy Yard, undated (Box 66)
  - Navy Yard, undated (Box 67)
  - Sham Battle, Van Cortlandt Park, 1902 (Box 67)
  - Dewey Naval Parade, 1899 Sep. 29 (Box 67)
  - Dewey Arch, 1899 Sep. 1-1899 Sep. 30 (Box 67)
  - New York Zoological Park, 1899 (Box 67)
  - Niagara, undated (Box 67)
  - Decoration Day, 1900 (Box 67)
  - Van Cortlandt Park, undated (Box 67)
  - Harlem River, undated (Box 67)
  - Houses, undated (Box 67)
  - State Camp, 1899 (Box 67)
  - Garrison, 1901-1902 (Box 67)
  - City Island, undated (Box 67)
  - Orchard Beach, City Island, 1909-1910 (Box 67)
  - Highbridge, undated (Box 67)
  - Family Portraits, undated (Box 67)
- Series III: Prints and manuscript material
  4 x 5" prints were matched to negative numbers and housed in boxes by number. Mounted prints (often duplicates of the loose prints) were grouped by subject and housed in folders. Copy prints made by N-YHS are housed after the vintage mounted prints. This Series also includes Stonebridge's logbook of photographs, and a number of his grammar school records and certificates of merit.
  - Bronx Park, 1902-1904 (Offsite-box 68)
  - [Washington Bridge], undated (Offsite-box 68)
  - Camp Block, 1898 May 14 (Offsite-box 68)
  - Fort Slocum, 1898 (Offsite-box 68)
  - [Decoration Day], 1903-1909 (Offsite-box 68)
  - Sham Battle, Van Cortlandt Park, 1897-1901 (Offsite-box 68)
  - Croton Cornell Dam Strike, 1900 Apr. 21 (Offsite-box 68)
  - 2nd Battery, 1899 (Offsite-box 68)
  - Navy Yard, undated (Offsite-box 68)
  - [Fordham, Bronx], undated (Offsite-box 68)
  - Van Cortlandt Park, Sham Battle, 1902 (Offsite-box 68)
  - West Point, 1908 Jun. 4 (Offsite-box 68)
  - Funeral of General Franz Sigel, 1902 Aug. 24 (Offsite-box 68)
  - Municipal Building], undated (Offsite-box 68)
  - [Miscellaneous Shoreline], undated (Offsite-box 68)
  - 2nd Battery, 1902-1903 (Offsite-box 68)
  - [Miscellaneous, unidentified images], undated (Offsite-box 68)
  - Porter Monument, 1902 Nov. 15 (Offsite-box 68)
  - [Snow House], 1905 Feb. (Offsite-box 68)
  - [Miscellaneous, unidentified images], undated (Offsite-box 68)
  - Dewey Naval Parade, 1899 Sep. 29 (Offsite-box 68)
  - Dewey Land Parade, 1899 Sep. 30 (Offsite-box 68)
  - Dewey Arch, 1899 Sep. 1-1899 Sep. 30 (Offsite-box 68)
  - New York Zoological Park, 1899-1902 (Offsite-box 68)
  - Niagara, undated (Offsite-box 68)
  - Decoration Day, 1899-1902 (Offsite-box 68)
  - Claremont Park, 1903 (Offsite-box 68)
  - Crotona, [1900] (Offsite-box 68)
  - Van Cortlandt Park, 1902-1906 (Offsite-box 68)
  - Riverside Park, 1897 Apr. (Offsite-box 69)
  - Lohbauers, 1898-1899 (Offsite-box 69)
  - Excursion, Roton Point, Locust Grove, 1903 Jul. 7 (Offsite-box 69)
  - May Walk, 1898-1899 (Offsite-box 69)
  - Excursion, Roton Point, Locust Grove, 1903 Jul. 7 (Offsite-box 69)
  - Cycle Parade, 1897-1898 (Offsite-box 69)
  - Speedway, undated (Offsite-box 69)
  - Coney Island, 1903 (Offsite-box 69)
  - Brooklyn Bridge, undated (Offsite-box 69)
  - Port Morris, Oak Point, undated (Offsite-box 69)
  - Harlem River, undated (Offsite-box 69)
  - Wrecks, 1902 Jun. 14 (Offsite-box 69)
  - Heine Fountain, Cornerstone, St. Joseph's, 1899 (Offsite-box 69)
  - 6th Heavy Artillery, undated (Offsite-box 69)
  - Fires, 1902 (Offsite-box 69)
  - Sportsman's Show, 1902 Mar. 15 (Offsite-box 69)
  - Hohenzollern, Stevens Airship, 1902 Nov. 4 (Offsite-box 69)
  - Botanical Garden, [1900] (Offsite-box 69)
  - [Stonebridge Family Gardens], undated (Offsite-box 69)
  - Tremont, [1902] (Offsite-box 69)
  - Fordham, undated (Offsite-box 69)
  - Pelham, City Island, Bartow, Westchester, undated (Offsite-box 69)
  - Houses, undated (Offsite-box 69)
  - Portraits, undated (Offsite-box 69)
  - Creedmoor, 1899-1904 (Offsite-box 69)
  - 2nd Battery, 1899 (Offsite-box 69)
  - State Camp, 1899-1904 (Offsite-box 69)
  - Garrison, 1900-1906 (Offsite-box 69)
  - Family Portraits, undated (Offsite-box 69)
  - [Liberty Bell], 1903 (Offsite-box 69)
  - [Ocean City, N.J.], undated (Offsite-box 69)
  - City Island, undated (Offsite-box 69)
  - Orchard Beach, City Island, 1907-1910 (Offsite-box 69)
  - Orchard Beach, City Island, 1909-1916 (Offsite-box 70)
  - Houses, undated (Offsite-box 70)
  - Hart's Island, 1903 Jul. 12 (Offsite-box 70)
  - [Maggie Nolan], 1903, Jul. 24 (Offsite-box 70)
  - Highbridge, [1900] (Offsite-box 70)
  - Clubs in the Bronx, undated (Offsite-box 70)
  - NY Central Railroad, 1903 (Offsite-box 70)
  - Gas Works, [1900] (Offsite-box 70)
  - Bridge under construction, [1903] (Offsite-box 70)
  - [Miscellaneous Bridges], undated (Offsite-box 70)
  - Echo Park Flag Raising, 1903 Nov. 26 (Offsite-box 70)
  - Excursion to Roton Point, undated (Offsite-box 70)
  - Manhattan, 1901 (Offsite-box 70)
  - [Poughkeepsie], undated (Offsite-box 70)
  - Manhattan, undated (Offsite-box 70)
  - Garrison, 1902-1910 (Offsite-box 70)
  - Churches, [1900] (Offsite-box 70)
  - State Camp, 1903-1915 (Offsite-box 70)
  - Portraits, undated (Offsite-box 70)
  - Bronx, 1903-1906 (Offsite-box 70)
  - Portraits, undated (Offsite-box 70)
  - Family Portraits, undated (Offsite-box 70)
  - [Bronx], undadted (Offsite-box 70)
  - [General Slocum Disaster], 1904 Jun. (Offsite-box 70)
  - Vintage print #3503, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 1)
  - Vintage prints, unnumbered, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 2)
  - Vintage mounted prints, The Bronx, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 3)
  - Vintage mounted prints, Bronx Park, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 4)
  - Vintage mounted prints, Cornell Dam Strike, 1900 Apr. 29 (Offsite-box 71, Folder 5)
  - Vintage mounted prints, Crotona Park, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 6)
  - Vintage mounted prints, Highbridge, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 7)
  - Vintage mounted prints, Historical Cards, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 8)
  - Vintage mounted prints, New York Zoological Park, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 9)
  - Vintage mounted prints, New York Zoological Park, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 10)
  - Vintage mounted prints, New York Zoological Park, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 11)
  - Vintage mounted prints, New York Zoological Park, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 12)
  - Vintage mounted prints, New York Zoological Park, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 13)
  - Vintage mounted prints, Snow House, 1905 Feb. (Offsite-box 71, Folder 14)
  - Vintage mounted prints, Unidentified Military, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 15)
  - Copy Prints, #s 1-2838, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 16)
  - Copy Prints, #s 2845-4249, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 17)
  - Copy Prints, #s 4250-4472, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 18)
  - Copy Prints, #s 4478-4835, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 19)